{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What company owns GitHub?",
            "answers": ["Microsoft", "Facebook","Google", "Amazon"],
            "correct":  ["Microsoft"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Is 'coupling' generally a good thing in software development?",
            "answers": ["Yes", "No","I don't know"],
            "correct":  ["No"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is a primitive data type in Java?",
            "answers": ["Integer", "int","String", "Object"],
            "correct":  ["int"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What company developed Flutter?",
            "answers": ["Microsoft", "It wasn't developed by a company","Google", "Facebook"],
            "correct":  ["Google"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What company developed React Native?",
            "answers": ["Microsoft", "It wasn't developed by a company","Google", "Facebook"],
            "correct":  ["Facebook"]
        }, 
        {
            "question": "What is the most interesting area in computer science?",
            "answers": ["Operating systems", "Optimization problems", "Handling errors", "Web development"],
            "correct": ["Web development"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following are programming languages? (Select all correct answers)",
            "answers": ["Python", "Photoshop", "Java", "HTML"],
            "correct": ["Python", "Java"]
        },
        {
            "question": "In Python, which of the following are used for creating a comment?(Can be more than one)",
            "answers": ["// Comment", "/* Comment */", " # Comment", " -- Comment"],
            "correct": ["# Comment"]
        },
        {
            "question": "In Python, which of the following are used for creating a comment? (Can be more than one)",
            "answers": ["// Comment", "/* Comment */", " # Comment", " -- Comment"],
            "correct": ["# Comment"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following are object-oriented programming principles? (Can be more than one)",
            "answers": ["Encapsulation", "Abstraction", "Modules", "Macros"],
            "correct": ["Encapsulation", "Abstraction"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does SQL stand for?",
            "answers": ["Structured Query Language", "Sequential Query Language", "Static Query Language", "Systematic Query Language"],
            "correct": ["Structured Query Language"] 
        },
        {
            "question": "What does SQL stand for?",
            "answers": ["isnull() function", " isempty() function", " is None keyword", "check_null() function"],
            "correct": ["is None keyword"] 
        }
        
    ]

}